Nica?
Nica. There's somebody
at the door. I'm busy.
Nica. please.
God!
What are you doing
that's so important?
I was playing solitaire.
The computer cheats.
you know.
Yeah. well.
I'm used to that.
Morning.
Hi.
Got a delivery
for Mrs. Sarah Pierce?
I'll... I'll sign for it.
Cool.
Whoa.
You know. you don't
look like a Mrs.
Oh. I'm...
I'm not. It's for my mother.
Oh. God. I'm back living
with my mother. too.
It's just a fucking
nightmare. right?
You have no idea.
Wait a minute. Oh. my God.
I know you.
Yeah. yeah. It was. uh. City
College. The Psych Department. right?
That was me.
Well. when'd you graduate?
I didn't.
I never completed my thesis.
Oh. on what?
Uh... Completion anxiety.
Thought only guys got that.
So. is your mom
home now or what?
Yeah.
Too bad.
Well. uh. see you around.
Bye.
Was that guy
hitting on me?
Baby. you're beautiful.
Thank you. But I... I think
that guy was hitting on me.
Maybe I should
go ask him out.
Nica.
He was just being nice.
I'm sorry.
Oh. honey. I just don't ever
want to see you get hurt.
I thought you swore off
the Home Shopping Network.
I haven't bought
anything in three weeks.
Maybe you have
a secret admirer.
You sound threatened.
No. Not at all.
I just wouldn't want
to see you get hurt.
Who's it from?
It doesn't say.
Must be some kind of joke.
I don't get it.
Neither do I.
He's cute.
If you say so.
Hi. I'm Chucky. Wanna play?
Alice will love him.
I DVR'd Real Housewives.
I'm going to make
tuna melts later. Okay?
Mom?
Oh. God.
Mom! No.
I need an ambulance right
away. It's my mother.
I don't know. I don't know.
There's so much blood.
Nica.
I'm sorry.
She was fine.
She was taking her meds.
she was painting again.
No. No.
She was fine.
How could she
do that. Barbie?
How could she do
that to herself?
You. uh...
You remember Father Frank.
Uh... Yes.
Hello. Father.
I'm so very sorry
for your loss. Nica.
Thank you.
Your sister just thought it might
be a good idea for me to come.
I appreciate it.
But you know my mother and I both
left the church a long time ago.
But not in the eyes of God.
I just thought
it might be nice
for us to have
someone to talk to.
We have each other.
Nica.
We have to pray for her.
To be forgiven.
She was sick.
You can't judge her.
No one is judging her.
In fact. the church's official
response to a situation like this
is not to judge. but to pity.
My mother and I have had
quite enough pity. thank you.
I understand.
It was my fault.
I should have
seen it coming.
Nica. you cannot
blame yourself.
She was supposed to
be taking care of you.
Hey.
Hey. lan.
Gimme a hug.
Is that a new chair?
Uh. yeah.
- It's cool.
- Thank you.
Uh. this... This is
Jill. my new au pair.
No. I'm just the nanny.
Hi.
I'm so sorry. Nica.
Thank you. I'm. uh.
I'm glad you're here.
Come here. you.
Oh...
I'm so happy to see you.
Me. too.
Did Grandma go to heaven?
Yes. sweetie. she did.
Hey. I have
a surprise for you.
That's funny.
Oh. Mommy.
I have to go to the bathroom.
Okay.
Jill will take you.
You show her the way. Mommy
needs to talk to Aunty Nica.
Jill. let's go.
Um... I think I'm going to
go with them. Okay?
Remember. you don't
have to lock the door.
But somebody
might come in.
We won't let anybody in.
But what about you guys? Hmm.
Honey. we really don't want to
see you do your business.
So listen. how much
is she paying you again?
$400 a week.
That's more
than I make.
Well. maybe you should
consider a career change.
Hey. I'd be a great nanny. $400 a week!
Man.
Yeah.
but no benefits.
What's your name?
Alice? Alice.
open the door. honey!
open the door right now.
He scared me
half to death.
What is this?
Well. um. Mom left
the house to both of us.
So?
So.
I think we should
consider selling.
What are you
talking about?
Nica. this place
is fabulous.
It's so much closer to us. we'd
get to see you way more often.
And with your half of what
we could get for the house.
you'd be set for
the rest of your life.
This isn't about me.
This is about money.
Well. you know
we've been struggling.
Print media is dead.
lan's working
at Starbucks.
We're going to have to
send Alice to public school.
And she so had her
heart set on St. Bridget's.
I don't want to
deprive my child.
You have a live-in nanny.
Well. actually. that's
not really working out.
Barb. this is my home.
Nica. I know
this is hard.
But do you really think you
can manage here all by yourself?
Mom would have wanted you
to be taken care of.
That's all she ever wanted.
We're back.
You found him.
He was in the bathroom.
Really?
You know. I think Grandma would
have wanted you to take care of him.
It was obviously
sent here by mistake.
It must belong
to someone else.
And Alice. you already have
too many dolls as it is.
Yeah. but Chucky's my
friend till the end!
I actually think it's a really
nice gesture. Thank you. Aunty Nica.
It's a doll.
What's the worst
that can happen. huh?
I like to be hugged.
I like to hug you.
too. Chucky.
Mmm...
What's that. Chucky?
Oh! Chucky wants to
know what's for dinner.
Well.
I guess I better get
started in the kitchen.
Oh. don't be silly.
Uh. you guys are my guests and you
must be exhausted from your flight.
please just make
yourselves at home.
Father Frank. you will stay
for dinner. won't you?
Well. I. uh...
I'd love to. Nica. Thanks.
Uh. you're going to
make dinner. For six.
Seven.
Well. I will need
a chef's assistant.
And Chucky can
be my assistant.
Great. Let's get cooking.
Mmm.
It's really good.
It's the oregano.
Did you finish
setting the table?
Almost.
Pay the toll.
We're on a roll.
Oh. no. honey. don't touch that.
Can you grab me the napkins?
The fancy ones
from last Christmas.
This smells delicious.
Thanks.
Come on. Chucky.
Wow. Look at this. Nica. You've
really outdone yourself this time.
We are going
to sit right here.
Barb.
sit next to me here.
Okay. If you insist.
Wow. Look at this.
Thanks. Jill.
Make yourself comfortable.
Oh. You brought out
the nice china.
Father.
would you like to say grace?
Bless us. oh Lord.
and these Thy gifts
which we are about to receive
from Thy bounty.
Stop. Through Jesus
Christ our Lord we pray.
Amen.
Jill?
Mmm. Thank you. lan.
Don't mind if I do.
How about you. Father?
Oh. no. I'm good.
I am starving.
Your daddy would
like to make a toast.
To the chef.
Thank you.
I had a great assistant.
I love chili.
Do you really?
Yeah.
Me. too. Love it.
Is there meat in this?
No. Not at all.
It's vegetarian.
Huh.
Oh. my God.
What?
I know. I can't believe
there's no meat in this.
It's so hearty.
It's the oregano.
This is just the way
my mama used to make it.
Nica. could you
pass me the salt?
Thank you.
You know. that doll. it
looks really familiar somehow.
Oh. Father. come on.
Good Guy dolls were all
the rage back in the '80s.
My brother even had one.
So did mine.
Are you serious?
Yes.
- Oh. come on.
- That is wild... I...
I seem to remember
seeing them on the news?
I remember seeing people
standing in line overnight
just to get their
hands on one of these.
They were right up there with
Smurfs and Cabbage Patch Kids.
Mmm.
Hmm. Hmm...
Alice. honey.
is something wrong?
It tastes funny.
Maybe we put too
much oregano in.
Alice. sweetheart.
it's not that bad.
Eat it.
Father. are you all right?
Oh. I'm...
I'm so sorry. I'm going
to have to be going.
Oh. my God.
Father. are you ill?
I have an appointment
back at the church.
Nica. thank you so much.
the chili was delicious.
Father. are you?
No. please forgive me.
I don't mean to be rude.
I'll see you all in
the morning at the cemetery.
Uh...
Good night.
I'm so sorry.
Where is he?
This way.
What happened?
Lost control.
hit them head on.
Probably drunk.
No. no. this isn't right.
I know him. I'm in his parish.
He doesn't drink anymore.
You sure about that?
He's my sponsor.
Stanton. you're going to need
a drink after you see this.
Jesus Christ.
Steel's got him pinned. He's
lost a shitload of blood.
but we just can't
tell from where.
Father. can you
hear me? Father?
Just hang on!
We're going to get you out.
What the hell are you waiting
for? Get this shit off him!
I can't make that call.
He's bleeding to death!
Get him out!
- Okay. set in.
- On my count.
One. two. pull.
Oh.
Oh. This is an oldie.
Oh. my God. Is that you?
Shut up.
You're so cute.
It's called baby fat.
Look. I didn't
say anything.
Go back to sleep.
Will do.
Look at her.
She's so happy.
What happened to your dad?
He drowned that year. couple
of weeks before Nica was born.
Mom was never
the same after that.
Who's that?
Some neighbor back
in Chicago. I guess.
What a weirdo.
Hey there.
missy. what'cha up to?
Chucky's gone.
Not again. Well. where
did you leave him?
I didn't. He's hiding.
Okay. time for bed.
And don't forget to brush
your teeth and your hair.
What about Chucky?
Jill will go look for Chucky.
I'll give you a hand. Jill.
Uh-uh. We're not done here yet.
I think he's
hiding under my bed.
Don't worry.
we'll find him.
I'm going to
be right back.
Are you sure you didn't
leave him downstairs?
I didn't leave him
anywhere. He's hiding.
There he goes!
I am not
in the mood for this.
Need a hand?
I need a fucking
search party!
I have looked over every inch of this
house and I can't find him anywhere.
God. I've missed you.
Shut up.
Oh...
You found him.
I think she
wanted you to find him.
You know. I haven't been
spending enough time with her.
It's like if I'm not working.
I'm just so tired all the time.
Life is short
Did they
always say that?
I don't know.
Listen. little man.
what else are you. uh.
telling my kid
behind my back. huh?
I like to be hugged.
Oh. And?
Hey. Wanna play?
Is that it?
Hi. I'm Chucky.
And I'm your
friend till the end.
That one's a classic.
Ah... And it works on so
many different levels.
Yeah. the '80s were awesome.
Did you find him yet?
Yeah. we found him!
I'll take him up.
lan?
Anyone?
Hello?
Oh. shit.
Coming!
See. with her.
it's always something.
She needs my help
and then resents me for it.
You're the only one
who really appreciates me.
You know.
I was thinking.
Hmm?
We can get by
without the money.
You don't have to sell.
I mean. this is her home.
She's a mess.
You can see that.
Oh. crap.
There you are. Chucky! We've
been looking for you everywhere.
Hey. want to play?
I didn't know
you could do that.
Playtime's over.
It's time for bed.
Can you read us
a bedtime story?
Aunty Nica's tired. sweetie.
We'll let her rest now.
I'm fine.
It's important that you
don't overextend yourself.
Don't you think
I'm the best judge
of when I'm
overextending myself?
Frankly. no.
Really.
I don't think you realize
the strain you're under.
There's no shame in
admitting that you need help.
You mean "assistance."
Nica. I am worried
about your heart. Okay?
Dr. Masur said
I was fine. Barb.
You're at significant risk of it
happening again. you know that.
13% of all
T5 paraplegics...
I know the statistics.
Dr. Masur said
that extreme stress.
any kind of even mild
shock could bring it on.
And since last night. God
knows you've had plenty of both.
Alice. sweetheart. please
come down from there.
I'm disabled.
Barb. I am not a child.
And I'm perfectly capable
of taking care of myself.
Aunty Nica.
you're bleeding.
Oh. my God.
I got it. Okay?
It almost looks
like a knife wound.
You must have cut
yourself making dinner.
I... I didn't.
Doesn't it hurt?
No. No. don't worry.
sweetie.
She can't feel a thing.
All right. come on.
Come on. Off to bed now.
Good night.
Aunty Nica.
Good night. baby.
Sweet dreams.
Now I lay me
down to sleep.
I pray the Lord
my soul to keep.
If I shall die before I wake.
I pray the Lord my soul to take.
God bless Grandma. and Mommy.
and Daddy. and Jill.
And especially Aunty Nica.
What about Chucky?
He says there is no God.
Who said that?
Chucky did.
He said that life's a bitch and then
you die. bleeding like a stuck pig.
Alice. You know
it's not nice to curse.
I don't curse. Mommy.
Chucky did.
Mommy. am I going to die?
No. Of course not. sweetie.
Grandma died. And Chucky
says we're all going to die.
Alice. who really
told you that?
Was it Jill?
No.
Was it your daddy?
No. it was Chucky.
Okay.
Can't we sleep in
with you tonight?
Alice. we've talked about
this. You're a big girl now.
It's only a storm.
And Jill's going
to be in in a while.
Don't forget Chucky!
Don't worry. Chucky.
It's only a storm.
- Ma'am. thank you for holding.
-  The package...
... evidence depository.
Um...
I'm... I'm sorry. you're breaking
up. Did you say "evidence depository"?
Hello? Hello. are you there?
Chucky. I'm scared.
You fucking should be.
Oh...
Sorry.
We found him.
She sure
loves that thing.
Yeah.
She sure does.
But you know. I just
called the delivery company.
and they said it was sent
from an evidence depository.
As in crime scene evidence?
I don't know. Maybe I heard them
wrong. The connection was bad.
I'm sure that's it.
Yeah. but we still
don't know who sent it.
I don't care if it
was the Manson Family.
Anything that keeps her
this happy is fine by me.
She's been so sad lately.
I better get to bed.
Long day tomorrow.
Uh... Good night.
Good night. Jill.
Andy Barclay.
Charles.
She's up.
Women.
Can't live with 'em. Period.
Shit.
What's going on?
Power's out again.
I'm going to go
check on Alice.
What about Jill?
What about her?
Well. come on. Barb.
You're paying her $400 a
week to take care of our kid.
Don't you think
she can handle it?
lan. she's afraid of the dark.
It's storming out.
She might need me.
Who. exactly.
might need you?
Who do you think?
Right now I'm not
sure what to think.
You know...
Don't try to implicate me
in your sick fantasies. okay?
I've seen the way
you look at her.
Ditto.
lan. I am not
sleeping with the nanny.
No. of course. you couldn't
be that stupid. Barb.
Knowing that if I
could prove such a thing.
I could easily take
Alice away from you.
Or I could just
check the footage.
What are you talking about?
The footage
from the nanny cam.
What nanny cam?
The one I hid in
the doll today.
You are not taking my daughter
away from me. Do you hear me?
I am not going to let
you destroy this family
because of your sick.
paranoid accusations.
Oh. that's right.
Tune me out.
Let Barb take
care of everything.
That's what you
always do anyway. right?
You latte-making loser.
What's the word
from Forensics?
Won't know anything   for sure
till they cook   his blood.
Hey. you talk to
anyone at St. Paul's yet?
Said he was out at
the Pierce house all day.
Okay. well. maybe they'll
have some answers for us.
I'm going to
head out there now.
Alice?
Alice! I don't have
time to play games.
Barb?
Barb!
Barb. where's Alice?
Playing fucking
hide and seek.
Barb. put him down.
Look. I know that this
sounds nuts. but that doll.
I think that there's
something in it.
Wait a second.
You know about this?
Well. I think that I do.
You know what's in this?
Do you?
Why didn't
you tell me?
I'm trying to tell you.
Wait. wait.
When did you find out?
What does it matter?
It matters to me.
It matters to me that my
own sister is out to get me.
No. No. no. no.
you don't understand. this...
Oh. I understand perfectly.
I understand you resent the
fact that I actually have a life.
No. Barb. this isn't
about anything that...
Well. you know what. Nica?
It isn't my fault. Okay?
What happened to
you isn't my fault.
And it isn't my fault that
you dropped out of school.
and it isn't my
fault that you chose
to never leave
this goddamned house.
I mean. what the hell were you
waiting for. a sign from God?
No. Barb! Just put
the fucking doll down!
Fuck you. Nica.
Barb!
Alice!
Get down here!
Jill?
lan!
Shit!
Alice?
Alice. don't touch anything.
You hear me?
Alice. you are in big trouble.
young lady!
Alice!
Alice. please.
Mommy is just about sick
to death of all of you.
Alice?
Alice. you come out
here right this minute.
Oh. my God.
Alice.
Alice is mine.
Now she knows
there is no God.
You have your mother's eyes.
And they were always too
fucking close together!
No!
Barbie?
Nica.
I'm gonna get you.
Alice!
lan! lan!
lan!
Wha... Huh? What?
lan. they're dead!
What are you talking about?
Barb. Jill. they're dead.
and I can't find Alice?
No! No! He's still out there!
Who?
Chucky!
Alice! Alice!
I gotta go find Alice.
lan. if you see Chucky. whatever
you do. just leave him alone.
Chuck...
What are you talking about?
Just stay away
from that doll!
Alice?
lan?
lan!
Alice?
lan! lan!
No!
Nica!
Nica. what the hell
are you doing?
He did it! It was him!
Nica! Look at me!
Give me the ax.
What? No!
Now. give me the goddamn ax!
Oh. my God.
Nica. what have you done?
lan. lan. please.
You know I would never...
Oh. my God.
lan. lan. Take this.
I need you to
inject it under my rib.
lan.
lan. lan. what are you doing?
What the hell have you
done with my daughter. Nica?
lan. where's Chucky?
You're sick!
lan. I swear to God.
I can prove it!
And so can I.
Hey. Barb. check this out.
RadioShack. 450 bucks.
Oh. and by the way.   if you're watching
this.   I put it on your MasterCard.
Where are you. Alice?
They'll never find
me in here. Chucky.
This is the best game
of hide and seek ever.
Just keep your
fucking mouth shut.
Chucky. stop cursing.
Say hi to
the little woman for me.
Maybe not.
Your turn.
My turn.
You're Charles Lee Ray.
My friends
call me Chucky.
You're dead.
No. you are.
Why us?
Didn't your
mother ever mention me?
I'm an old
friend of the family.
Charles.
come over here.
I wanna introduce
you to someone.
October 27th.
Okay.
Right against
my rib cage.
Soon enough.
Cannot come soon enough.
Charles. this is Sarah.
Hi.
How do you do?
Her husband. Daniel.
Hello. sir.
Hi. Daniel.
Nice to meet you.
And this is Barb.
She has her mother's eyes.
Such a nice.
happy family.
But not for long.
You like 'em?
Mmm-hmm.
They're beautiful.
thank you.
Difficult to find right now.
They're not exactly in season.
Anyway. enjoy.
It's gettin' late. and I'm gonna
go pick up Barbie at day-care.
No!
I mean. shouldn't we have
some time alone together?
What about family time?
Later.
Right now I want to
have you all to myself.
Sarah. Sarah.
you've had me all day.
It isn't enough.
That's a selfish fucking
attitude for a mother to take.
You don't wanna
share me with her?
No. No.
Well. what's gonna happen
when the baby comes?
Are you gonna keep
her from me. too?
Because that would
be very hurtful to me.
And you wouldn't wanna
see me get hurt. would you?
Would you?
No. No.
I don't wanna
see you get hurt.
I don't wanna see
anybody get hurt.
Okay.
I'm gonna go get Barbie.
No! Please. please!
Please don't.
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
You told them about us?
There is no us.
Why?
Why would you want to
destroy this family?
You destroyed my family.
No.
I told you.
I've always had
a thing for families.
No!
Especially kids.
You did this to me?
No. Nica.
you did this to me.
You and your mommy.
She betrayed me.
Got me killed.
But I knew a way to come back.
Give me the power.
I beg of you!
Took me 25 years.
but believe me.
it was worth the wait.
Twenty-five years.
Since then. a lot of
families have come and gone.
The Barclays.
the Kincaids. the Tillys.
but Nica. your family
was always my favorite.
And now.
you're the last one standing.
So to speak.
You know. you remind me
a lot of Andy Barclay.
He was a whiny little bitch.
just like you.
Did you kill him. too?
More or less.
I killed his childhood.
And the truth is.
I killed you 25 years ago.
Didn't I. Nica?
You haven't been living.
You can't call this living.
You've just been
on life support.
Time to pull the fucking plug.
So you never actually
killed Andy Barclay. did you?
What?
You know. it's called
completion anxiety.
It's very common in males.
You are a male.
aren't you?
Oh...
I'm gonna kill you slow.
Yeah. no. I get that.
Twenty-five years. Must be
the slowest murder in history.
I mean. what are you
waiting for? A sign from God?
No!
You feel that. don't ya?
You wanna play.
motherfucker? Let's play.
Police. Open up.
Help! Help me!
Based on the evidence.
the defendant
is declared
legally incompetent
and remanded indefinitely   the criminally insane.
I'm alive. you son of a bitch.
You hear me?
I'm still alive!
Hey. it's me. I'm on my way.
And don't forget my money.
They never learn.
So who's next?
Next.
Good afternoon.
Three-day.
two-day. or overnight?
Overnight.
It's extremely urgent.
Fragile?
Surprisingly not.
Approximate value?
Well. my mother always used to
say you can't put a price on love.
Under 250. then.
Would you like to
insure the package?
Oh. that won't be necessary.
It protects you and it
protects the recipient.
I doubt that.
Perishable goods?
Live animal?
Just put "other."
Grandma. I'm home.
Grandma?
Oh. I'm fine. I'm fine.
Oh. that's great. Bunny.
As you know.
Bunny has won 17.000...
Chucky. you found me!
I told you I would.
Where's Grandma?
In the cellar.
What's she doing
down there?
Nothin'.
Chucky. Mommy
and Daddy are dead.
Aunty Nica killed them.
But I'm your friend
till the end. Alice.
And now it's time to play.
Hide and seek?
Hide the soul.
And guess what?
You're it.
Why do I always
have to be it?
Because you're somebody that
no one would ever suspect.
Now. close your eyes.
Give me the power.
I beg of you.
Package for you.
Really?
Maybe you won something.
Must be my lucky day.
Have a good one.
Thanks. You. too.
Oh. boy. A seat!
Hey!
Get your seat
off of my feet.
But what feet?
Hello? Oh. hi. Mom.
how you doing?
I'm sorry I didn't call.
I meant to.
Yeah. I'm definitely coming
for my birthday tomorrow.
No. don't get me anything.
Do me a favor.
Ma. no surprises. okay?
Yeah. I'll be there.
like. noon? 1:00?
What are you
making for dinner?
Yeah?
How's Mike doing?
Well. tell him I said hello.
Um... Yeah.
All right.
Come on. open up. open up!
Well. I'll see you
around that time.
Okay.
Yeah.
Aha!
Play with this.
Andy...